<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
<channel>
  <title>Decentralizing Capitalism</title>
  <link>https://www.decentralizingcapitalism.com/</link>
  <description>An ambitious community-driven show inspired by the reshaping our capital markets, monetary system, and labor organization. Driven by the ethos of decentralizing knowledge, founder John Wooten aims to make investments as accessible and open to everyone as information and money are through TCP/IP and blockchain. You can join our mission of empowering the next generation by adding your own episode through a PR on this show's GitHub page. Tune in to learn how you can be part of this revolutionary movement towards a decentralized economy.</description>
  <itunes:image href="https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/imgs/design/icon.png"/>
  <itunes:author>Community Contributors</itunes:author>
  <itunes:email>hi@wootenwealth.com</itunes:email>
  <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:category text="Technology"/>
  <language>en-us</language>
  
  <!-- INSERT YOUR NEW EPISODE HERE
  <item>
    <title>YOUR EPISODE NAME HERE | DISPLAY NAME</title>
    <description>YOUR RSS DESCRIPTION HERE</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/{n}.html</link>
    <enclosure url="https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/audio/{n}.m4a" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/audio/{n}.m4a</guid>
    <pubDate>DAY, NUM MON 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>HOUR:MIN:SEC</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>
  -->
  
  <item>
    <title>John Wooten at al: New SEC Short-Sale Reporting Rules and Implications | Ankit Sehgal</title>
    <description>Discusses the intricacies of the new short sale reporting rules, which were delayed by up to a year just four days after this recording. We also chat on currency decentralization.</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/6</link>
    <enclosure url="https://bafybeif6hgpzw2btxuzoxlj32cqwmhn5vyfnndeevk5kzof7zmwaqx3xry.ipfs.dweb.link" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeif6hgpzw2btxuzoxlj32cqwmhn5vyfnndeevk5kzof7zmwaqx3xry.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>1:37:6</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>John Wooten at al: What is Decentralization? Case Study of an Onchain Launch After Gensler | Ankit Sehgal</title>
    <description>Today we dive into the recent public offering of an AI company through a coin listed on Coinbase within hours of trading. John contemplates the implications of insider trading activity on decentralized exchanges, which was centrally investigated and punished by an underlying core team. We extrapolate this turn of events to ask ourselves, "What is decentralization," with plenty of stories to go along from community contributors!</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/5</link>
    <enclosure url="2:48:17" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeihy32wxqmf5rt6kzm3ue4u72btt6vcyyabcpnkd2sf23nljs2qohu.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>HOUR:MIN:SEC</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>John Wooten: Regulation Showdown Between FINRA, the SEC, and Congress | Ankit Sehgal</title>
    <description>In exploring the past of securities regulations and their general social frameworks, we discuss often-overlooked key goals of public policy as developed over the course of centuries. Looking forward, we finish with a chat on the regulation of TAD3 using a first-of-its-kind DUNA community reconciliation model. Uncover the principles behind today's best practices that just might leave you scratching your head.</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/4</link>
    <enclosure url="https://bafybeidp3qmqdqm254uwbrzmo2to5bzoserjxcny4wbc7owp32uhiry4dy.ipfs.dweb.link" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeidp3qmqdqm254uwbrzmo2to5bzoserjxcny4wbc7owp32uhiry4dy.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>1:23:48</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>John Wooten et al: ETF and Central Banking Abuse Methods Demystified | Ankit Sehgal</title>
    <description>This episode delves into the detailed mechanisms of exchange-traded funds in the context of central banking practices, examining the role of centralized credit unions, the structuring of fiat access systems, and the sophisticated processes of block creation and redemption often leveraged in strategies like short selling. By unpacking these interconnected systems, we uncover the underlying dynamics shaping financial market operations and their broader implications.</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/3</link>
    <enclosure url="https://bafybeib6la56yw6vbqwa75k5aesws2leel72avbcmfw77fy6p4iszggqrq.ipfs.dweb.link" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeib6la56yw6vbqwa75k5aesws2leel72avbcmfw77fy6p4iszggqrq.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 5 Dec 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>1:20:45</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>John Wooten et al: How Should We Govern the Financial System? | Ankit Sehgal</title>
    <description>In this episode, we examine the emergence of new banking structures and the foundational role governance plays in their success. We highlight the launch of the first American DUNA (nonprofit DAO) organization, a pioneering effort to redefine financial networks through transparent, decentralized systems. From the challenges of aligning stakeholders to the critical importance of system governance, we explore how these innovative structures are reshaping the financial landscape and creating new opportunities for inclusivity and accountability.</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/2</link>
    <enclosure url="https://bafybeidma4ayfojhfdulelim6eha7l75gkxy2lgvgtjza2cm7nagmkwkkm.ipfs.dweb.link" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeidma4ayfojhfdulelim6eha7l75gkxy2lgvgtjza2cm7nagmkwkkm.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>1:34:49</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>John Wooten: Global Moves to Curtail U.S. Investor Protections | Ankit Sehgal</title>
    <description>In this episode, we explore how Singapore, Switzerland, and China are leveraging tokenized treasuries and blockchain innovations to sidestep traditional U.S. investor protection laws. Using UBS's upcoming tokenized treasuries as a case study, we analyze the global shift in financial strategies and what it means for American investors.</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/1</link>
    <enclosure url="https://bafybeictesuhxtqip6zmfjvwejusrdrtexxemfrccshe54bxjwviafjhtq.ipfs.dweb.link" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeictesuhxtqip6zmfjvwejusrdrtexxemfrccshe54bxjwviafjhtq.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>1:27:11</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Genesis: Why Decentralize Capitalism? | John Wooten</title>
    <description>In this episode, we discuss the inspiration of this show.</description>
    <link>https://decentralizingcapitalism.com/articles/0.html</link>
    <enclosure url="https://bafybeigc7ffss6vlbqawbuj3kdvvc7ftgbe7oaq7oxxoggmqh4tkqnebce.ipfs.dweb.link" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://bafybeigc7ffss6vlbqawbuj3kdvvc7ftgbe7oaq7oxxoggmqh4tkqnebce.ipfs.dweb.link</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:duration>1:41:15</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>
